<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="PhasmoGhostsSchema.xsd" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema"?>
<PhasmophobiaGhosts>
    <Evidences>
        <Evidence>
            <Id>EMF-5</Id>
            <Name>EMF 5</Name>
            <Mechanics>When a ghost with EMF Level 5 as one of its evidences interacts with the environment, the EMF reading will have a 25% chance to be an EMF 5 emission instead of EMF 2 or EMF 3, which can be detected and confirmed with an EMF Reader.</Mechanics>
        </Evidence>
        <Evidence>
            <Id>Orb</Id>
            <Name>Ghost Orb</Name>
            <Mechanics>When a map is loaded in, Ghost Orbs will spawn in the favourite room and float within the room. They look like very small orbs that glide across the screen, generally one at a time. They can be seen through the screen on a Video Camera with night vision, or through any available video feed with night vision.

Depending on the map and the location of the favourite room, Ghost Orbs can sometimes be seen via the map's CCTVs if the CCTV happens to be facing into the favourite room, though this is usually rare. Ghost Orbs will periodically shift position within the favourite room, forcing players to be more proactive in locating them.

When the ghost room changes on difficulties where 'Changing favourite room' is not set to 'None' (such as on Professional and Nightmare), the Ghost Orbs will also move to the new favourite room.</Mechanics>
        </Evidence>
        <Evidence>
            <Id>SpiritBox</Id>
            <Name>Spirit Box</Name>
            <Mechanics>The Spirit Box is considered an electronic equipment. When interfered with, all the LEDs/icons will flicker rapidly. Holding an active Spirit Box within 7.5 metres of a ghost on the same floor will attract it to the player.

Note that the ghost may still respond audibly if the player asks questions while the Spirit Box is being interfered with. This also counts as Spirit Box evidence.

There is too many information about this device. Check wiki for mor info: https://phasmophobia.fandom.com/wiki/Spirit_Box</Mechanics>
        </Evidence>
        <Evidence>
            <Id>Freezing</Id>
            <Name>Freezing</Name>
            <Mechanics>The presence of a ghost in a room will cause the room's temperature to decrease, regardless of evidence. Ghosts without Freezing Temperatures evidence will be able to drop the room's temperature to 1°C (33.8°F), whereas ghosts with Freezing Temperatures as evidence will be able to drop the temperature to −10°C (14°F).

When the temperature drops to 5°C (41°F) or below, the players may be able to see their own breath; this does not necessarily mean that the ghost will have Freezing Temperatures as evidence. Freezing Temperatures can only be confirmed if the thermometer reads a temperature strictly below 1°C (33.8°F).

If using a Tier I thermometer, Freezing Temperatures can only be confirmed if the thermometer reads a temperature strictly below 0°C (32°F) as it is less accurate.</Mechanics>
        </Evidence>
        <Evidence>
            <Id>Ultraviolet</Id>
            <Name>Ultraviolet</Name>
            <Mechanics>Ultraviolet evidence consists of fingerprints and footprints which can be revealed by using a UV Light.

Each interaction on a valid surface will always produce a fingerprint or a footprint (except for the Obake which has a 25% chance to hide them).

Additionally, the Obake can sometimes use an ability to reduce the remaining time for all existing fingerprints and footprints on the map by half.</Mechanics>
        </Evidence>
        <Evidence>
            <Id>Writing</Id>
            <Name>Writing</Name>
            <Mechanics>If Ghost Writing is a piece of evidence, if the ghost chooses to interact with an opened ghost writing book, the book will rise and frantic scribbling will be visible.

There are six different types of Ghost Writing that a ghost can put in the book. Each has an equal chance of occurring and the type of writing does not narrow down the type of ghost any more than the fact that the ghost writes in the book at all. Each book may contain different types of writing.</Mechanics>
        </Evidence>
        <Evidence>
            <Id>DOTS</Id>
            <Name>D.O.T.S</Name>
            <Mechanics>The D.O.T.S Projector can be placed (default: F on keyboard) on a wall or floor similar to a motion sensor. It emits a matrix of bright green laser points in a small area from the projector. Tier I D.O.T.S Projector additionally can be held and toggled (default: right click on mouse) to create a cone of D.O.T.S light where it is pointed.

Ghosts with D.O.T.S evidence will occasionally enter a 'D.O.T.S state'. During this, a faint silhouette of the ghost will be visible only when it passes through the laser grid. The ghost will also walk towards the nearest player if there is one in the same room, or towards a random waypoint if no players are nearby. While these silhouettes are visible to the naked eye (unless the ghost is a Goryo), a video camera with night vision may allow for better visibility. This also means that D.O.T.S can be tracked simultaneously alongside Ghost Orbs. Dead players cannot see D.O.T.S by any means.

Though the D.O.T.S Projector is an electronic equipment, only the Tier I D.O.T.S. Projector when activated and held will attract the ghost to the player during a hunt, and they are otherwise safe to hold onto.</Mechanics>
        </Evidence>
    </Evidences>
    <Ghosts>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Banshee</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Unique Screech</Name>
                    <Description>When a Parabolic Microphone is used, the Banshee has a 33% chance of making a unique shriek-like paranormal sound instead of a whisper or footstep.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Frequent singing ghost event</Name>
                    <Description>Performs melodic ghost events more often than other ghost types</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Roaming to target</Name>
                    <Description>When the Banshee performs a roam, if the target is inside the investigation area, it has a 2/3 (67%) chance of roaming to the target. This does not occur during hunts.

This can result in a very high ability count on the post-game statistics. The roam cannot be completed if the player is on a different floor.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Special condition of hunting</Name>
                    <Description>The Banshee's hunt threshold is 50%, but it only checks the target's sanity when trying to hunt, rather than the average sanity like other ghost types, meaning that only the target needs to be at or below 50% sanity for it to attempt to hunt.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Special hunting behavior</Name>
                    <Description>When a Banshee hunts, it will mostly follow standard hunt rules, but it will ignore all players other than its hunt target. It will not attempt to chase other players nor will it kill them, even if it comes into direct contact with a non-target player, instead passing through them.

If the hunt target is outside the building, the Banshee will still use the target's sanity to decide whether to hunt. However, if it does hunt, it will hunt like any other ghost, chasing any opportune player.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Demon</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Sanity independent hunt</Name>
                    <Description>The Demon has an ability that allows it to automatically start a hunt, regardless of current average sanity. There is no particular behaviour or condition (such as requiring line-of-sight with a player) that affects if it activates or not; if it decides to use its ability, it will hunt. This hunt can be blocked by normal prevention methods.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Lesser hunt cooldown</Name>
                    <Description>Demons have a minimum cooldown of 20 seconds between hunts, instead of the usual 25 seconds.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Smudging prevents hunts for shorter</Name>
                    <Description>Smudging a Demon will prevent hunts for only 60 seconds, as opposed to the standard 90 seconds.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Larger effective range of a crucifix</Name>
                    <Description>
4.5 metres instead of 3 for Tier I
6 metres instead of 4 for Tier II
7.5 metres instead of 5 for Tier III</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>70</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Deogen</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Unique response through the Spirit Box</Name>
                    <Description>If the player asks any question through the Spirit Box while standing within 1 metre of the Deogen, it has a 33% chance with each question to produce a unique response of constant heavy bull-like breathing, instead of a regular response.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Spirit box is required on the nightmare or higher</Name>
                    <Description>On difficulties with only 1 or 2 evidences (e.g. Nightmare), the Deogen always has Spirit Box as one of its pieces of evidence due to its unique response.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Different speed during hunts</Name>
                    <Description>When the Deogen is chasing a player, its speed is based on its pathfinding distance to the target player and has three thresholds: above 6 meters, between 6 and 2.5 meters and below 2.5 meters.
More than 6m: 3 m/s
Between 2.5 - 6m: Assumed speed gradient between 0.4 - 3 m/s
Less than 2.5m: 0.4 m/s

If the Deogen is smudged or is otherwise not chasing any player, its speed will remain at its current speed, or 1.6 m/s if its current speed is greater than 3 m/s. Otherwise, the Deogen does not alter its speed based on line-of-sight while chasing a player.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Always knows where players are during a hunt</Name>
                    <Description>When the hunt begins, the Deogen will pick the nearest player (by straight-line distance) to move towards. It will occasionally "refresh" and repick the nearest target throughout the hunt. One can also use Incense to stun the Deogen temporarily and force it to change its target when the smudge effect runs out.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Unique blink frequency</Name>
                    <Description>During a hunt, the Deogen's flickering is on average invisible for shorter and visible for longer</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>40</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Quickly rushing down players during a hunt no matter where they are, but is slow to approach when closing in for the kill.</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Invisible for shorter and visible for longer</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Goryo</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Short roams</Name>
                    <Description>When performing a roam, the Goryo can only perform short roams, rather than either short or long roams.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Goryo cannot change favorite rooms</Name>
                    <Description>The Goryo cannot change favorite rooms by itself in any difficulty. This can be overridden via the sanity wish when using the Monkey Paw.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>D.O.T.S. is required on the nightmare or higher</Name>
                    <Description>On limited evidence (1/2 evidence) games, a Goryo will always have the D.O.T.S. Projector as one of its evidence types.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>D.O.T.S silhouette is only visible through a Video Camera</Name>
                    <Description>The Goryo will only be seen in a D.O.T.S state if no players are in the same room as the ghost. In addition, its D.O.T.S silhouette is only visible through a Video Camera, and cannot be seen with the naked eye. A Goryo will still manifest normally during ghost events and hunts with its ghost model, which does not require any special equipment to be seen.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Hantu</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Moves quicker in colder areas during hunts</Name>
                    <Description>During a hunt, the Hantu's speed is affected by the temperature of the room that it goes through:

                Room temperature	            Ghost speed (m/s)
                More than 15°C                     	1.4
                12°C to 15°C                      	     1.75
                9°C to 12°C                     	         2.1
                6°C to 9°C                      	          2.3
                3°C to 6°C                      	          2.4
                0°C to 3°C                  	              2.5
                Lesser than 0°C                  	   2.7</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Freezing temperatures are required on the nightmare or higher</Name>
                    <Description>On limited evidence (1/2 evidence) games, a Hantu will always have Freezing Temperatures as one of its evidence types.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Freezing breath when the breaker is off</Name>
                    <Description>When the Hantu's ghost model is visible during a hunt, it will emit freezing breath near its head in any room as long as the breaker is off. Dead players cannot see this breath.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Depends on the temperature</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Jinn</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>The Jinn cannot turn off a breaker</Name>
                    <Description>The Jinn cannot turn off a breaker directly through interacting with it. The fuse box can still be turned off by overloading, whether by the player or the Jinn (unintentionally).</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can lower the sanity of all players within 3 meters of it by 25%</Name>
                    <Description>When the Jinn uses its ability and the fuse box is on, it will lower the sanity of all players in the same room or otherwise within 3 meters of it by 25%. An EMF 2/5 reading will be generated at the fuse box.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Different speed during hunts</Name>
                    <Description>During a hunt, if all of the following three criteria are satisfied:

1. The fuse box is turned on;
2. The Jinn has line-of-sight with a player it is targeting;
3. The Jinn is further than 3 metres from that player.

Then its speed will be fixed at 2.5 m/s while the criteria are met. Otherwise, it will obey standard ghost speeds.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Fast during chase if it is far away from the player, but has normal speed otherwise.</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Mare</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Different hunting starting sanity when lights are turned off</Name>
                    <Description>If the lights are turned off, the hunt sanity threshold is increased to 60%, and if the lights are turned on, the threshold is decreased to 40%. This applies even if the fuse box is turned off or broken, but not if the room's lights are destroyed. Other sources of light, such as brought-in equipment and Firelights, do not affect this threshold.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Turns off lights and breaks lightbulbs more often</Name>
                    <Description>Mares cannot interact with lights to turn them on (this excludes computer monitors and televisions), and they are more likely to choose turning off lights as an interaction.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Mares cannot interact with lights to turn them on (this excludes computer monitors and televisions)</Name>
                    <Description>Mares cannot interact with lights to turn them on (this excludes computer monitors and televisions)</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Chance of turning the light off almost immediately</Name>
                    <Description>If a player turns on a light that is within 4 metres of a Mare, it has a small chance of turning the light off almost immediately. There is a minimum cooldown of 10 seconds between the light being turned on, which will restart if it is turned on before the 10 seconds is up. This also applies for televisions and computers.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Lights on</Name>
                    <Value>40</Value>
                </Condition>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Lights off</Name>
                    <Value>60</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Moroi</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Spirit box is required on nightmare or higher</Name>
                    <Description>On limited evidence (1/2 evidence) games, the Moroi will always have Spirit Box as one of its evidence types.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can curse players through the spirit box or the parabolic microphone, making them lose sanity faster</Name>
                    <Description>The Moroi has an ability to "curse" a target through the following ways:

By successfully obtaining a response from the Spirit Box; this will curse the person who "caused" the response, either by asking questions or triggering the failsafe.
By hearing whispers through the parabolic microphone.

When a player is cursed, their passive sanity drain is doubled, being in a lit area will no longer prevent sanity drain. Walking outside of the investigation area will still pause sanity drain until they enter again. Consuming Sanity Medication removes the curse for that player. Players that have been cursed before in the contract can be cursed again. Multiple players can be cursed at the same time, but curses do not stack on a single player.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Different speed during hunts</Name>
                    <Description>The Moroi's speed is dependent on the average sanity at the beginning of the hunt. The base speed increases by an average of 0.083 m/s for every 5% average sanity below its average hunt threshold of 50%.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Will be disoriented for longer when smudged during a hunt</Name>
                    <Description>When using an Incense during a hunt, the duration where the Moroi cannot see nor kill players is 7.5 seconds instead of 5.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Depends on sanity</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Myling</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Produces paranormal sounds more frequently</Name>
                    <Description>The Myling produces paranormal sounds (that can only be heard through a Parabolic Microphone) more often than other ghosts.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Has quieter footsteps and vocalizations during hunts</Name>
                    <Description>When hunting, a Myling's footstep and vocalizations sounds will only be audible to players within 12 meters, slightly greater than the range required for electronic interference, instead of the usual 20 meters. The volume of footsteps is slightly muffled near the limit, but quickly becomes discernible as it approaches.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Obake</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can leave a unique fingerprint pattern</Name>
                    <Description>When creating handprints or fingerprints, there is a one-sixth (~16.7%) chance for the Obake to create a unique handprint/fingerprint pattern:

1. A six-fingered handprint instead of the usual five fingers
2. Two fingerprints on a light switch instead of one
3. Five fingerprints on keyboards and Prison cell doors instead of four</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Occasionally fails to leave fingerprints</Name>
                    <Description>Each time the Obake interacts with a valid surface, it has a 75% chance of leaving Ultraviolet evidence, instead of the usual 100%.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Fingerprints can disappear faster than usual</Name>
                    <Description>The Obake occasionally triggers an ability to reduce the remaining time for all existing fingerprints and footprints on the map by half. For example, two fingerprints lingering on the map with 40 seconds and 70 seconds before timing out and disappearing are cut in half to 20 and 35 seconds remaining respectively. This ability can be triggered multiple times in quick succession, making it possible for an instance of fingerprints to last for mere seconds before vanishing.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Ultraviolet is required on nightmare or higher</Name>
                    <Description>On limited evidence (1/2 evidence) games, an Obake will always have Fingerprints as one of its evidence types. This does not affect its ability to occasionally not leave fingerprints and footprints on a surface.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Has a chance to blink in a different ghost model when hunting</Name>
                    <Description>During a hunt, the Obake has a 1/15 (6.67%) chance each time it flickers to shapeshift into a different ghost model of the same gender.  It will then return back to its original model. This is guaranteed to happen at least once per hunt. Dead players cannot see this shapeshift. The ghost changing into a different posture (e.g. going from standing to crawling) within a hunt, while otherwise retaining the same model, is also considered a shapeshift.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Oni</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>More active when people are nearby</Name>
                    <Description>On average, the Oni is more active, interacting with objects more often, especially when there are people in the ghost room.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Prefer showing in its full form during a manifestation event</Name>
                    <Description>Will prefer showing in its full form during a manifestation event as opposed to a shadowy or translucent form.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Cannot produce "airball" ghost events</Name>
                    <Description>Cannot perform the "airball" event, which involves a physical ball of fog moving towards the player, usually disappearing with a hiss sound upon collision. Note that chasing events can similarly cause a hiss.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Model remains visible for longer periods when hunting</Name>
                    <Description>During a Hunt, an Oni will flash visible for longer than most other ghosts, making it easier to take a photo of.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Oni will flash visible for longer than most other ghosts</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Onryo</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Blows out fiery objects (candles, campfire) more often with more dead people</Name>
                    <Description>If a player is currently dead, the Onryo will blow out sources of flame (lit firelight, igniter, or campfire) at a higher frequency. More dead players increases this frequency. It will blow out flames at the same frequency as other ghosts if no players are dead.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Presence of flames prevents the ghost from hunting</Name>
                    <Description>If the Onryo attempts a hunt within 4 metres of any type of flame, it will blow out the flame instead, and the hunt will fail. This does not restart the hunt cooldown timer, unlike a crucifix. If both a crucifix and a flame are within range, the flame will take priority over the crucifix for preventing the hunt.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Chance to hunt at any sanity after blowing out a flame</Name>
                    <Description>Every third flame that the Onryo blows out will cause it to attempt to initiate a hunt, regardless of current average sanity. This hunt can be blocked by normal prevention methods (e.g. a crucifix) or another flame.
                    
1. Note that there can be a delay of up to ~6 seconds before the hunt actually initiates.
2. If a flame prevents a hunt or is blown out during a hunt, it will count towards the three-flame rule.
3. Whether it was the same item being blown out does not matter; it can be the same firelight blown out 3 times, 3 firelights each blown out 1 time, or any other combination.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Every third flame that the Onryo blows out will cause it to attempt to initiate a hunt, regardless of current average sanity</Name>
                    <Value>100</Value>
                </Condition>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>60</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Phantom</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Ghost is invisible in a photo</Name>
                    <Description>If a successful photo is a taken of a Phantom, either in its physical form or when it appears in the D.O.T.S. Projector light, the ghost will be invisible  in the photo, and the photo will not contain any interference.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Special behavior of the ghost when a photo is taken during a ghost event</Name>
                    <Description>1. The ghost will physically disappear
2. Electronic equipment will cease to malfunction
3. Players will no longer hear their heartbeats
4. The event sound will continue to play for the duration of the event</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Seeing the ghost nearby during manifestations and hunts drains more sanity</Name>
                    <Description>Being within 10 metres of a Phantom while in pseudo line-of-sight (where heartbeats play) reduces the player's sanity by 0.5%/s. This only applies during ghost events and hunts, and is separate from passive sanity drain. This does not apply during ghost events if the Phantom was made invisible by taking a picture.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Occasionally roams to a random player</Name>
                    <Description>The Phantom has an ability where it will choose a random player and travel to their location (as opposed to a regular roam). This will create an EMF Level 2 reading at the targeted location. This behavior is somewhat similar to that of the Banshee and the Wraith; unlike Banshees, Phantoms do not select a player to target until they die or leave the game, and do not do this as often; and unlike Wraiths, the Phantom physically walks to that point rather than teleporting, and will set off Motion Sensors and disturb Salt on the way to it.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Remains invisible for longer periods when hunting</Name>
                    <Description>During a hunt, a Phantom will flash visible every 1 to 2 seconds, as opposed to every 0.3 to 1 second for other ghosts, making it harder to take a photo of.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Remains invisible for longer periods when hunting</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Poltergeist</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can throw a single object farther than other types</Name>
                    <Description>Occasionally, the Poltergeist will throw an item with a "force" value of 2 - 6, instead of 1 - 3 with other ghosts.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>The Poltergeist is more likely to throw items</Name>
                    <Description>In general, the Poltergeist is more likely to throw items. During a hunt, the Poltergeist will always throw an item every 0.5 seconds, instead of only having a 50% chance to do so.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can throw multiple objects at once</Name>
                    <Description>The Poltergeist will occasionally use an ability that allows it to throw multiple nearby items at once, creating an EMF level 2 reading (the thrown items themselves generate EMF 3). This will decrease the sanity of all nearby players in line-of-sight with the EMF 2 location by a percentage equal to the number of items thrown multiplied by 2. The ability and associated sanity drain works even when the lights are turned on.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Raiju</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Active electronics boost its speed during hunts</Name>
                    <Description>During hunts, if the Raiju is within a certain distance of at least once piece of active electronic equipment, it will move at a fixed speed of 2.5 m/s.
This also applies for items outside the investigation area, but not for items across floors.
All effects listed above apply to most electronic equipment, both when held in the hand and items dropped on the floor.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Disrupts electronics from further away when manifesting</Name>
                    <Description>When a Raiju manifests during a ghost event or a hunt, it will interfere with electronics that are up to 15 metres away on the same floor, instead of the usual 10 metres.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Nearby at least one piece of active electronic equipment</Name>
                    <Value>65</Value>
                </Condition>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>There is no active electronic equipment</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Active electronics boost its speed during hunts</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Revenant</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Significant speed increase when chasing a player during hunts</Name>
                    <Description>Revenants have very noticeable speed change between roaming and chasing modes. When a Revenant is roaming, it will move at 1 m/s. However, as soon as it detects a player (either visually or through speech/electronics), it will begin to move at 3 m/s (nearly twice the base speed of most other ghosts) and sustains this speed until it reaches the spot where it last detected a player. If and when reverting to roaming mode, the Revenant's speed will slowly decrease over ~2.7 seconds (deceleration rate of 0.75 m/s²) back to its initial value of 1 m/s.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Roam mode: slow
Chasing mode: fast</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Shade</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Harder to find due to it being generally less active</Name>
                    <Description>The Shade is less likely to perform ghost events at high sanity. At 100% average sanity, it has a 0% chance of successfully performing an event. This success rate increases by 2% per percentage of average sanity lost; at an average sanity of 50%, an attempted ghost event will always succeed.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Produces hissing and shadowy form ghost events more often</Name>
                    <Description>When it performs a ghost event, the Shade has a higher chance (67% per event) of performing a "ghost mist" ghost event rather than manifestations. If it does manifest for a ghost event, it has a higher chance (67%) of appearing as a shadow. If the ghost is made to appear using a Summoning Circle, a Music Box, or a Monkey Paw, it has a chance of appearing as a black shadow rather than in its full form while in the ghost event stage. It will return to a fully visible form when the hunt begins.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Generally unwilling to hunt and perform interactions in the presence of players</Name>
                    <Description>If at least one person is in the same room as a Shade, it will be unable to perform regular interactions (except Ghost Writing) or initiate a hunt, regardless of average sanity. It may still perform these actions if it happens to wander into a room without players. Since interactions occur in a range, the Shade can still "reach" into the player's room from another room to interact with objects.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>35</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Spirit</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Lit smudge sticks double the hunt cooldown</Name>
                    <Description> When Incense is used near a Spirit, it will not be able to initiate a hunt for 180 seconds instead of 90 seconds with most other ghosts. Like other ghosts, this will not prevent cursed hunts. This delay will still apply if the Spirit was smudged while already hunting.
                    </Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Thaye</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Writing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Abilities of the ghost depend on it's age</Name>
                    <Description>The Thaye has an internal "age" parameter that affects its general activity.
Every 1 to 2 minutes, the Thaye attempts to age; if at least one player is in the same room as the ghost, the Thaye will add 1 to its age, else it will wait another 30 seconds before attempting to age again.
Per age added:
-6% Hunt sanity threshold
-0.175 m/s Hunt speed
-15% Relative interaction/ghost event rate	</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Very active and fast at the start</Name>
                    <Description>With age 0 thaye has this parameters:
Hunt sanity threshold: 75%
Hunt speed: 2.75 m/s
Relative interaction/ghost event rate: 200%	</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Age 0</Name>
                    <Value>75</Value>
                </Condition>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Age 4</Name>
                    <Value>51</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Depends on the age</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>The Mimic</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Ultraviolet</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Will always produce false ghost orbs</Name>
                    <Description>The Mimic provides "evidence" of Ghost Orbs in addition to its three main evidence types, which also appear on Nightmare difficulty and on custom difficulties with reduced evidences, including zero evidence. These Ghost Orbs, along with the other evidences if none are hidden due to the difficulty, will always exist regardless of the type of ghost that The Mimic chooses to imitate.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Mimics other ghost types one after another for brief periods of time</Name>
                    <Description>The Mimic is able to imitate any type of ghost, and inherit all of its features and abilities:

-Interaction and ghost event rates and preferences
-Hunt thresholds
-Hunt movement speeds
-Various forms of special abilities (e.g. Poltergeist multithrow, Demon
ability hunt)

The Mimic will change the ghost type that it chooses to imitate every 30 seconds to 2 minutes, but cannot change during hunts. If The Mimic mimics a Thaye, a fixed age is randomly selected, and it will mimic another ghost using its own timer instead of the Thaye's ageing timer. The Mimic may also imitate the player or The Mimic (itself), but in these cases, it will act as a "default" ghost and have no special abilities. Mimicking the player, as well as any other ghost, does not change its ghost model.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can copy features of evidence of mimicked ghost</Name>
                    <Description>It may also copy features of evidence of mimicked ghost types, but not their evidences themselves. For example, it is able to copy the Obake's six-fingered handprints as The Mimic itself has Ultraviolet as evidence, but it cannot copy the Goryo's trait of only appearing on a Video Camera when interacting with a D.O.T.S Projector, as The Mimic does not have D.O.T.S. Projector as one of its evidences. </Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can't copy guaranteed evidence on reduced evidence difficulty</Name>
                    <Description>It cannot copy other ghost types' guaranteed evidences on Nightmare/reduced evidence types custom difficulty, even if The Mimic has them as evidence.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Every third flame that the Onryo blows out will cause it to attempt to initiate a hunt, regardless of current average sanity</Name>
                    <Value>100</Value>
                </Condition>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Yokai triggering sanity</Name>
                    <Value>80</Value>
                </Condition>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Thaye hunting sanity</Name>
                    <Value>75</Value>
                </Condition>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Depends on mimicking type of ghost</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>The Twins</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can interact with the environment simultaneously</Name>
                    <Description>When The Twins uses its ability, it will perform one interaction in the normal radius (up to 3 metres) and one within a larger radius (up to 16 metres). All such interactions follow the standard 25% chance of producing EMF 5 instead of 2 or 3, regardless of which radius was used to perform the interaction.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can hunt from a different place than expected</Name>
                    <Description>When The Twins attempts to initiate a hunt, there is a 50% chance for it begin at its current location, and a 50% chance for it to begin close to the area where it last interacted using its ability. Regardless of where The Twins hunts from, it will follow standard hunting rules. As The Twins is only one ghost, two hunts cannot occur simultaneously, and it will follow the standard 25 second cooldown between hunts.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Differing speeds depending on which twin hunts</Name>
                    <Description>Depending on where the hunt begins from, The Twins will move at two different speeds. If it hunts from its present location, it will have a base speed of 1.5 m/s, and if it hunts from the area where its large radius interaction occurred, it will have a base speed of 1.9 m/s.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Slow or fast depending on where the hunt begins from</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Wraith</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>EMF-5</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Never steps in a salt</Name>
                    <Description>The Wraith will never step in a salt pile, and therefore will never disturb them. This includes Tier III Salt during hunts, rendering it ineffective against one.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can teleport to a random player, becoming active near them, outside of ghost events and hunts</Name>
                    <Description>When the Wraith is not hunting, it has a chance to teleport within 3 metres of a random player, generating an EMF Level 2 reading at the location where it teleported to, with a 25% chance for this to be an EMF Level 5 reading instead. The Wraith will resume normal behaviour after teleporting.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Yokai</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>SpiritBox</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Talking near it will increase its chance of hunting and interaction rate</Name>
                    <Description>When at least one player uses voice chat within a certain range of the Yokai, its hunt sanity threshold is temporarily increased to 80%. Otherwise, it has the standard threshold of 50%.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Can only hear voices and detect electronics within a short range</Name>
                    <Description>During hunts, a Yokai can only hear players or sense handheld active electronics that are within 2.5 meters of it. Its line-of-sight is unaffected.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Talking around Yokai</Name>
                    <Value>80</Value>
                </Condition>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
        <Ghost>
            <Name>Yurei</Name>
            <GhostEvidences>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Orb</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>Freezing</RefId>
                </Evidence>
                <Evidence>
                    <RefId>DOTS</RefId>
                </Evidence>
            </GhostEvidences>
            <SpecialAbilities>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>Will be temporarily confined to its room after smudging</Name>
                    <Description>When Incense is used on the Yurei, in addition to preventing hunts and temporarily increasing activity, it will return to its favourite room and be trapped in it for 60 seconds. It can still leave that room by performing a ghost event, but it will return to it once the event ends.</Description>
                </Ability>
                <Ability>
                    <Name>May randomly shut a door and deduct nearby players' sanity</Name>
                    <Description>The Yurei has an ability that will cause the following when used:

- All players within 7.5 metres of the ghost will have their sanity decreased by 15%. Players outside the investigation area will not be affected by the sanity drain.
- If the ghost's current room has one or more open door, it will randomly select one and close it fully. This in turn produces an EMF 2 interaction, just like any other door touch.
    1. The Yurei cannot use its ability if the room it is in has no door.
    2. All ghosts can shut a door from in the same way the Yurei can, however the Yurei may do it more often as it is connected to its sanity drain ability.
- Locker and closet doors are not affected by the Yurei's ability. Tent doors, however, are.
                    
If the ghost shuts a front door (exit door) fully without a ghost event or hunt, then it is definitely a Yurei.</Description>
                </Ability>
            </SpecialAbilities>
            <HuntStartingSanity>
                <Condition>
                    <Name>Default</Name>
                    <Value>50</Value>
                </Condition>
            </HuntStartingSanity>
            <Speed>Default</Speed>
            <BlinkFrequency>Default</BlinkFrequency>
        </Ghost>
    </Ghosts>
</PhasmophobiaGhosts>